Guide to the Herbert L. Abrams Papers SC0858
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2014-108
  - Publications and Manuscripts
    - The Fallout from Chernobyl - final manuscript. Bul. Atomic Scient., Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Health Technology Assessment: The Problems and the Challenge, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Hidden Illness in the White House - review by HLA NYT, Jan. 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - "How Stable are the Nuke Handl?" - Times Tribune, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Human Instability & Nuclear Weapons. Bull Atom Scientists, Undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Version of Human Instability Presnted at the IOM, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Human Reliability & Safety...In the Handling of Nuclear Weapons, 1991 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Human Reliability & Safety in Handling of Nuclear Weapons - Sc. & Glob. Security, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Human Reliability, Instability, & Control of Nuclear Weapons - Copenhagen (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Inescapable Risk: Human Disability & "Acc."Nuc. War - Smoker Journal, Undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - The IPPNW: A Single Issue Organ - Letter in Science, Mar. 1988 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - IPPNW Congress Talk: The Problem of Acc./ or Inad. Nuc. War, Undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - IPPNW Congress Talk presented: Chernobyl and the short term medical effects of nuclear war., Undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Computed Tomography of the Kidney, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Computed Tomography of the Kidney - Seltzer, Huber, Abrams, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Blank Conference Forms, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Computed Tomography Versus Ultrasound of the Adrenal Gland: Prospective Study, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Computed Tomography Versus Ultrasound of the Adrenal Gland, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript - Hessel et al. Prospectiv Evaluation of CT & US of the Pancreas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript - Coronary Vascular Patterns During Occulusion Arteriography. Spindola-Franco Fldh. Adams and Abrams, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript - Doubilet, Abrams, The Cost of Underutilization: Percutaneous Transluminal Angioplasty, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Percutaneous Trtansluminal Angioplasty Correspondence, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The Cost of Underutilization, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Mass Lesions: A DX Approach to Renal Vasc. Tumors & Cysts. J. Con. Ed., Mar/Apr. 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript - Editoral. The Doctor's Dilemma, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript - The Economic Cost of Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript - Evaluation of Left Ventricular on Chest Radiographs, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript - The Golden Era of Radiology Is There Enough Gold, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Hemodynamically Significant Anomalies of the Coronary Arteries - Angiographic Aspects. Levin/Fellows/Abrams, 28494 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript - History of Future of Interventional Angiocardiography, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - State-of-the Art Imaging of Pulmonary Embolic Disease, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - From David P. Dalzell, 35977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Radiology Centennial, 1995-96 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Caldemeyer et al rec'd, Oct. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Author status, Jun. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - PGR Answers, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Office Information, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Trace File, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Work to Do, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Filing Cabinets, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Filing Papers, Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Cardiac Radiology, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Melvyl Medline Plus, Undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Misc. papers, Undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - PGR Manuscripts, Undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Editorial Comments in Journal of Continuing Education in Radiology and Postgraduate Radiology, 1979-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Pulmonary Artery Anomalies - Reports and Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Articles about Regan Shooting/Incapacitated Presidents, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Slides
    - Research in Radiology: A Hollistic Perspective Sept. 29 1994, 1981-2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ductus as an Avenue of Escape, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Slides - Ebstein's Anomoly; Anomalies of Pulmonary Venous Return, 1978 Dec. 7 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ethical Issues in Tech. Assess. 7 Utilization, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Slide The Golden Era of Radiology, 1988 May 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Slide Funtional Correlates of Morpholgic Change, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Slide Gastrointestinal Bleeding, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Slide Heart, Acquired Disease, 1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Slide Tumors, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Slide Hypertension, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - The Illusion of Long-term Survival, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Slide Imaging Methods in Heart Disease, 1979 June (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Slide Imaging Systems in Cardiovascular Disease: A Critque, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Slide Inferiror Mesenteric Arteriography, 1977 Oct. 10 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Slide Impact of New Technologies of Angiography, 1978 June (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Japan "From Icons to Ions and Back": Sept/Oct. 1989, 1989 Sept.-Oct. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - From Icons to Icons & Back" UCSF May 13, 1989, 1989 May 13 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Slide Kidney, Cysts, and Tumors, 1977 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Slide Left Main Coronary Disease Slide List, 1975-1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Left Heart Obstruction Syndrome, 1978 Dec. 14 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Slide Medico-legal Aspects of Angiography, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Slide Coronary Artery Disease, 1977 Nov. 11 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Slide Main Left Coronary Artery Disease, 1979 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Slide Coronary Teaching File, 1982 May (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Slide Coronary Arteriography: A Critical Evaluation, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Coronary Arteriography, China, 1983 April 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Present Status & Pitfalls of Cor. Arter. LIJH, 1988 Oct. 27 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Pitfalls in Cor. Arteriog. - Harvard 1987, 1987 June 15 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Slide Pitfalls in Cornary Arteriography HMS P.G. May 27. 82, 1982 May 27 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Speech "Pitfalls in Coronary Arteriography" - PG Course May 82, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Slide List, Coronary Arteriog. Harvard Course - 1987, 1987 June 15 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Slide Coronary Arteriography, Evaluation of, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Slide List Critical Evaluation of Coronary Artery Disease, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Critical Evaluation Imaging Methods, 1979 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Slide Coronary Circulation, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Cost of Bias and Clinical Decision Making, 1981 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Slide Dissecting Aortic Aneurysm A Diagnostic & Therapeutic Problem, 1975-1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Computed Angio-Tomography: It's Impact on Decision, 1981 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Computed Angio-Tomography: It's Impact on Angiography, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Slide-Computed Angio-Tomography, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - CT Presentation Slide Folder, 1977 Dec. 5 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - CT of the Ardenal, 1982 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Computed Tomography in Neoplastic, 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - CT in Oncologic Disease, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Slides CT of the Kidney, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Contrast Enhancement in Ct, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Congenital Heart Disease Resident Review May 23 1982, 1982 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Slide Congenital Heart Disease, 1972-1984 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Congential Valvular Disease (Pulmonic, Mitral, Aortic Stenosis, and Insufficiency), 1978 Oct. 19 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - cavography and Venography Angio Conference Talk 11/8/79, 1979 Nov. 8 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Certificate of Need and Regulatory Agencies, 1978 Sept. 25 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - China Trip - Grand Rounds June 1983, 1983 June (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Collateral Circulation, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Complications of Coronary Disease, 1979 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Complications of Coronary Disease, 1977 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Complications of Myocardial Infarction, 1980 Jan. 26 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Complications of Myocardial Infarction: Aneurysm, 1977 Oct. 10 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - The Complications of Myocardial Infarction: Aneurysm, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Angiography In Acquired Heart Disease, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Speech Folder: The Complications of Myocardial Infarction, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Angiography for Diagnosis of Cardiac Emergencies, 1984 Mar. 6 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Amgiography in Oliguric Rental States, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Aortic Arch Anomalies, 1973 May (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - The Significance of Asymptomatic Disease, 1978 Nov. 30 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Recent Advances in Diagnosis of Cancer, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Cardiac of Scanning, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Slide folder: Cases, 1977 Oct. 31 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Slides We Do Not Have, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Critical Care Medicine Symposium, 1984 Mar. 6 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Heart Failure, Lungs In, 1977 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Slides:Abnormalities of the Pulmonary Circulation, 1978 Oct. 18 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Acquired and Congenital Abnormalities of the Pulmonary Arteries, 1977 Oct. 21 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Acute Radiation Syndrome, 1982 Mar. 11 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Present Status of Adrenal Imaging, 1981 Sept.4 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Miscellaneous Slide List For Speeches, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - MRI: Development of Natural Consensus, 1988 May 3 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Neoplastic Disease: Problems in the Evaluation Process, undated (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Oliguria, 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Oncologic Disease--Problems, 1980 Mar. 7 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Neoplastic Disease: Problems in the Evaluation Process, 1981 Jul. 8 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Pathology & Radiology of Arteriosclerotic CV Disease, 1980 Sept. 8 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Speech: The Roentgen Pathology of Coronary Disease, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Pathophysiology Questions, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Speech & HMS Pathophysiology Course, 1984 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Normal Heart, undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Normal Cardiovascular Dynamics, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Pharmacoangiography Historical Aspects, 1987 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Pharmacology of Vessels in Neoplasia, 1973 Mar. 19 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Plain Films In the Diagnosis of Congential Heart Disease, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Liver Tumors (DX OF), 1978 Feb. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Lymphangiography & Lymphoma, 1975 Jun. 16 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Lungs in Heart Failure, 1979 Oct. 11 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Lungs In Heart Failure and Pulmonary Hypertension, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Magnification Angiography: Theory and Practice, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Medical Efficacy of Diagnostic Radiology Utilization Study, Apr. 14 & 15 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Medical Legal Aspects of Angiography, 1983 Oct. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Medical Problems of Survivors of Nucelar War, 1982 May 11 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Medical, Social, & Econoomic Implications of CT, 1980 Apr. 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Medical, Social, & Econoomic Implications of CT, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Tumor Circulation: An Analysis and Review, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Tumor Vessels: Effect of Vasconstrictors, 1978 Mar. 24 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Urography--Usefulness of The 1, 3, and 6 Film Examinations, 1979 Jan. 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Pathophysilogic Basis of Ventricular Wall Function, 1977 Oct. 31 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Renal Vascular Bed in Hypertension, 1976-1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Screening Methods in Removing Hypertension, 1975 Oct. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Renal Trauma, 27 Feb. 1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Renal Venography, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Renal Venography: Refresher Course, 1981 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Speech Role of CT in Medical Practice, 1980 May (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Soviet Visit 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Angiography of the Spleen, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Spleen Trauma, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Supravalvular Aortic Stenosis, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Technology Assessment & MRI-Japan 1989, 1989 Oct. (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Technology Assessment & MRI-Japan 1989, 1989 Oct. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Technology Assesment in Health Care: Problems and Challenges, 1990 Apr. 2 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Ethical Issues in Technology Assessment and Utilization, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Throacic Aortography, 1979 Oct. 4 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Slide Lists: Preclinical Medicine Course 4/9/92, 1992 Apr. 9 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - The Prominent Pulmonary Artery Segment, 1990 Apr. 12 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - The Prominent Pulmonary Artery Segment 10/81, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - PSR Annual Mtg. 1988 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Pulmonary Hypertension & Increased Pulmonary Blood Flow, 1975 Oct. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Puzzles & Pleasures in the Diagnosis of Heart Disease, 1974 Sept. 30 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Quantitative Derivates of Renal Radiologic Studies, 1973 Mar. 19 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Radiologic Research: A Holistic Perspective, 1980 Apr. 4 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Radiography and Angiography of the Heart, 1973-1980 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Radiology of Arterioscolerosis, 1982 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Tetralogy of Fallot; Pulmonic Stenosis Plus Patent Foramen Ovale, Double Outlet Right Ventricle Radiology of Heart Failure, 1978 Nov. 2 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Radiology of Valvular Heart Disease, 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - The Radiology of Heart Disease, 1979 Jan. 18 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Radiology Imaging: Pros and Cons, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Radiology of the Pancreas, 1978 Feb. & 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Radiology of Heart Failure 1982, 1982 Nov. (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - The Radiology of Heart Failure Refresher Course, 1978 Nov. 11 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Referral Criteria Conference, 1978 Oct. 25 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Renal Angiography in The Era of Cross Secional Imagaing, 1991 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Renal Arteriography, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Renal Artery, Dyplasia, & Renovascular Hypertension, 1983 Apr. (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Radiology of Renal Transplanation, 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Slides on Patients, The Radiologic Process (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Pitfalls - Coronary Arteriography - Right (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Pulmonary Hypertension (Accidental or Inadvertant Nuclear War) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Pulmonary Hypertension - Lecture, 1997 June (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Anomalies (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Pitfalls in Coronary Arteriography - Left (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 2 Slide Carousels - Normal Cardiovascular Dynamics & Radiology of Atheriosclerosis (Left) and Renal Venography (Box 16)
    - 3 Slide Carousels - Heart Failure, Dissection (Right), and Renal Veins with RV Hypertension (Box 17)
    - 3 Slide Carousels - Research in Radiology, Acyanotic Heart Disease (Box 18)
    - 3 Slide Carousels - Cyanotic Heart Disease, Heart Failure (Right), Normal Cardiac and Heart Failure (Box 19)
    - Persistent Fetal Ductal Flow: The Ductus as an Avenue of Escape (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Coronary Disease (Left) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Angio in Cardiac Emergencies (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Renal Angiography in the Era of Cross Sectional Imaging (Right) (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Angiography in the era of cross sectional imaging (Left), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 3 Slide Carousels - Congenital Heart Disease, CT in Oncology (Right), 1990 May (Box 21)
    - 2 Slide Carousels - Normal Cardiovascular Dynamics & Radiology of Atherioscleriosis (Box 26)
    - Slides of Various Coronary Diseases (1/2) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Slides of Various Coronary Diseases (2/2) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Slides of Various Patient Anomalies (1/2) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Slides of Various Patient Anomalies (2/2) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Slides, circa 1997 (Box 29)
    - Slide Lists and Lectures for Ethical Issues in Tech Assessment Class, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Pathophysiology Course: The Radiology of Valvular Heart Disease and Heart Failure - Slide List and Lectures, 1984 Sept (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Speeches
    - Acute Radiation Syndrome, 1982 Mar. 11 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Advances in Computerized Imagaing, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Radiology of Adrenal, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - The Present Status of Adrenal Imaging, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - American Heart Association, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Pathophysiology Course - Harvard Medical School, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Radiology of Heart Disease - Book Outline and Notes (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Research in Radiology Speech, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Prominent Pulmonary Artery Segment - Course Outline, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Radiologic Anatomy and Pathology Course, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - China Visit, 1983 April 10-23 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - A Season of Change: Legacy of the Sixties - Speech (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cardiovascular Imaging: Past, Present and Future - Speech, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Radiology of Heart Failure - Slide List and Speech, 1984 Apr 20 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Aoritc Dissection (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - The Kidney in Hypertension, 1982 Oct (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Health Technology Assessment Papers, 1987-1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Trips to Alaska and Europe, 1958-1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Abrams - Talks, Meetings and Conferences, 1970-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear War Interviews and Newspaper Articles, 1981-1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Einthoven Meeting on Past & Present Cardiology (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Radiology (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Speech: The Prominent Pulmonary Artery Segment (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - American College of Radiology, 1991 Sep (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Speech Folder: Pulmonary flow & resistance (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Slide List-Coronary Arteriography (Harvard), 1987 Jun (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Golden Era of Radiology: Is there Enough Gold?, 1988 May (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Pulmonary Vascular Disease (1 of 2), 1956-1978 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pulmonary Vascular Disease (2 of 2), circa 1970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Pathophysiology 7010, Cardiovascular (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Pathophysiology 7010, Cardiovascular (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Postgraduate Radiology-Editorial Comments, 1984-1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Postgraduate Radiology-Editor's Comments, 1984-1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Postgraduate Radiology - Chronological File, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Address and Contacts (Rolodex files) (Box 32)
  - Portrait, 1998 Jun (Box 33)
  - Audiovisual material
    - The Health of Presidents, 2000; 28.1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 28)
    - Paul Mimicks, 28.2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 28)
    - Allen Hensworth, 1967 Jul 7; 28.3; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Kenedy Daniel, 28.4; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - John Cestone, 1973 Nov 15; 28.5; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Endocardial, 28.6; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Beating Heart, 28.7; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Banding, 28.8; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Kennedy Daniel Copy, 28.9; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Endomyocardial Fibrosis African, 28.10; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - John Cestone (Diagnosis), 1973 Nov 15; 28.11; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Debbie Morris, 28.12; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Phrase Flow, 28.13; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Hypoplastic Left Heart Syndrome, 1967 Aug 18; 28.14; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Rider Steven, 1966 Jun 22; 28.15; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Complications in Selective Coronary Arteriography, 28.16; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - PDA, 28.17; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Aortic Insulficiency & USD, 28.18; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Anornalous Origin of Left coronary, 28.19; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Coronary AV Fistula, 28.20; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Tricuspid Stenou, 28.21; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Pulmonic, 28.22; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Aortic, 28.23; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Supravalrular Arotic, 28.24; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Interuption of the Artic Arch, 28.25; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Tetralogy of Pallot, 28.26; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Pulmonic, 28.27; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Ebstein, 28.28; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Corrected Transposition, 28.29; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 28)
    - Tremous, 28.30; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Eisen., 28.31; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Single Ventricle, 28.32; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Total Anomalour, 28.33; 1 film reel(s) (8mm) (Box 28)
    - Untitled, 28.34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 28)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-044
  - Risk Reduction (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Risk Reduction (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Travel/Cartoons/Quotes (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Travel/Cartoons/Quotes (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Travel/Cartoons/Quotes (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear War (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear War (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear War (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear War (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear War (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear War (Supporting Docs Index) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear War (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear War (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear War (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Untitled negatives (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Untitled negatives (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Duplicate Slides (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Untitled negatives (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chernobyl, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Soviet slides (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dissection left (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Coronary Arteriograph for Arizona (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Radio Experiment (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Seminar, 4/23/1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Coronary Arteriography - Right (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - China (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Untitled negatives (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Untitled negatives (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dissection right (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pakistan, Afghanistan News (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Korea (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pakistan (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ISI, Kashmir, al. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ISI, Taliban (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Regional Conflicts and Nuclear War (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Afganistan (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - China (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - India (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - India - Delivery (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Iraq (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Israel (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pakistan - Nuclear Weapons (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pakistan PRP (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Reagan Transition Success (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pakistan Nuclear Weapons (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Pakistan - Doctrine (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pakistan Clippings (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Pakistan Safety (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Pakistan Emergency Response (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Pakistan Delivery (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Proliferation (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - U.S. - Cuban Missile Crisis (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Russian Dismantlement (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Instability (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dangers / Risks of (Box 3, Folder 27)